architecturaldepot.com 2015-12-19

# Privacy Policy: ArchitecturalDepot.com -- Your Privacy & Rights -- by Architectural Depot - Call us today at: 888-573-3768

## Your Privacy and Rights

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **CAN-SPAM Compliance**

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

 **Information about Teracent Cookies**

To further enhance the users experience we have partnered with Teracent for their expertise in increasing user experience. If you would like to opt-out of this service, please [click here](http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out/) to opt-out.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.architecturaldepot.com/help-terms.html.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on **August 1st, 2012**

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.ArchitecturalDepot.com  
505 W. Lambert Road  
Brea, CA 92821  
United States  
j.morris@architecturaldepot.com  
888-573-3768

 **Privacy Policy Customer Pledge**

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commision Fair  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the [Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form](http://secure.trust-guard.com/disputesystem/). 

Respectfully, 

James Morris Team Member  
www.architecturaldepot.com

### Return Policy

You may return most items purchased from ArchitecturalDepot.com for partial refund within 30 days from purchase date. All returns are subject to a 20% restocking fee. All returns must accompanied by an RMA or RGA and be in resalable condition and received within 14 business days from authorized return date. You can obtain an RMA or RGA by contacting customer service at 888-573-3768.

Custom Products: We are pleased to offer architectural products that are custom-manufactured to your specifications, and we encourage you to review your order carefully. Since the product is built to your specifications, the order cannot be changed, modified, or canceled once your order is in production.

Custom products include, but are not limited to: Custom vinyl shutters, custom wood shutters, custom crossheads, custom pediments, and other custom products. If you have a question of whether or not the item you would like to order is custom, please contact us prior to ordering.

WE CANNOT ACCEPT RETURNS FOR CUSTOM PRODUCTS

Important Information About Your Shipment: Upon receiving your shipment, please inspect the items carefully for damaged or missing items. All shipping claims must be handled within 72 hours of receiving your order. Claims made after 72 hours will not be honored. If you received your order damaged, defective, or an incorrect item please contact our customer service department at 888-573-3768.

If you have any questions regarding our returns policy, please feel free to contact us at 888-573-3768 or 714-706-4370. Thank you, ArchitecturalDepot.com
